geekwant.com 2017-04-15

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

This policy covers Geekwant's use of personal information collected when you use www.Geekwant.com. We are careful to only use the information you provide us in the way that you authorize to do so. If you have any queries about the practices then please Contact Us. This privacy policy may be updated online at any time. Please review this page regularly so that you are aware of any changes made.

Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect and store the details provided by you when you choose to fill out a form on the website. Any information stored is used only for the purposes of improving our service. We do not disclose your personal identifiable information to any third parties.

Cookies

A cookie is a small mount of data that is sent to your browser from a website and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each website can send it's own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookie it has already sent you, not the cookies sent to you by other websites. Cookies record information about your online preferences. Users have the opportunity to set their computers to accept all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn more about how to change your cookie preferences. We use cookies on the Geekwant website to save your preferences for the look and feel of the site. We use cookies to store your favourite games. We also use cookies to notify you when there is a new piece of content on the site. We store "keep me logged in" preferences in cookies. Advertisements on Geekwant.com or any sub-sites may also use cookies. We DO NOT store any personally identifiable information in cookies that we set.

Flash Shared Object

We use Flash Shared Objects (sometimes known as Flash Cookies) within all of our games for the purposes of saving your progress or information required by each game. This information is stored on your own computer and is not available to anyone else.

Advertisements

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These third-party advertising companies may use cookies to serve you advertisements.

Other Websites

Our website contains links to other websites which are outside the control of Geekwant Limited and therefore not covered by policies set by Geekwant Limited. If you visit a third-party website using the links provided within Geekwant.com then the operators of those websites may collect information from you in accordance with their own privacy policy.

Facebook Connect

Some services and features on the Geekwant.com website allow you to connect to your Facebook account. We use this feature to enhance the social aspect of Geekwant.com. As Facebook is a third-party website, we advise you to review Facebook's Privacy Policy. By registering via Facebook Connect, you give us express permission to receive data from Facebook including, but not limited to, your name, user ID, gender, location, email address, date of birth and avatar. For Facebook Connect users we store your email address, user ID, date of birth and gender and other information based on your use of our Service.

Children's Privacy

We do not allow any user under the age of 13 to register on Geekwant. If a user chooses to register they must be at least 13 years old. Users are asked for a date of birth upon registering. This is to prevent visitors under the age of 13 from creating accounts.

Messages and Comments

To help protect your privacy, please do not post any personally identifiable information on the Geekwant.com website.

IP Addresses

Geekwant.com may also collect your IP address for safety and security purposes. An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the internet

Newsletters

If you wish to sign up to our free newsletter service, you will be asked to supply personal information sush as your e-mail address. With your permission, Geekwant.com uses such information to periodically contact you with product information news, special offers and new games that are released.

Opt out

If you are receiving e-mails from Geekwant.com (newsletters, special offers, game release notifications) and would like to later opt out. Please click the unsubscribe link from within the newsletter to remove your email from the newsletter mailing list.
